I can change for the better. I know I can.
I can be someone who makes a difference.
Do you think you can save her?
What have I done?
We... what have we done?
No!
Back up. You just told us Iroha was missing? When did that happen?
Please, Mifuyu. If you know anything about Iroha or the Magius' plan, we need you to tell us. Before it's too late.
Nothing would change if I did.
It might.
I knew, and it didn't matter. Things happened. Things that can't be undone now. In the end, I wish I never knew anything.
If I knew about any of this, I would have tried to stop it from happening.
All we can do now is quit the Magius!
This is all wrong. If my friends are in danger, I don't want to be kept in the dark about it.
And if this is the end of everything, I want to be with them, not in a place like this.
Yeah, screw them, I guess. If Iroha and the others were in trouble, I should have known about it!
You're right. If only I had your courage, I could have chosen my fate, too.
What do you mean? Choose it now, it's not too late!
Yeah, totally. Come home with us if you want.
I can come with you?
Sure. Back to Mikazuki Villa.
We still need to find Tsuruno. I hope she's okay.
Don't worry, she's still alive.
That's a relief.
Oh, thank goodness.
After everything, I don't expect you to trust me. But if you do, leave Tsuruno to me.
I'll find her, and bring her back to Mikazuki Villa.
Iroha...
Ui! Where are you?
I'm over here. This way. Hurry!
Ui!
Kurue...
Hang on, Ui. I'll find you. But first, I have to find Nemu and Toka.
Ui!
There's so many witches. Why are they here?
Watch out!
Sorry about that!
I didn't hit you, did I?
She's okay, but I came close to having a heart attack.
Well, we meet again.
Yeah, and this time, I brought along some friends.
Okay...
Sorry, but that sounds totally crazy.
The Magius want witches to come to Kamehama?
Yes. And they convinced an army of magical girls of the plan, to make sure no one interfered with it.
How could they believe this is right?
They were tricked, of course.
The Magius say they're the key to our salvation, and as long as you're loyal to them, you won't turn into a witch.
You mean they can't do that?
You mean they can't do that? It's all just a lie?
Yes. A lie spread by girls who can't accept their fate.
The price we paid for our wishes can't be cancelled so easily.
Iroha, thank god.
Are you okay? Where are you?
I'm in Magius' theme park, on the teacup ride.
Huh?
I'm okay, they can't see me here.
But things are looking really bad.
More and more witches keep showing up.
The little Kyubei was with me, but he took off.
I got separated from Kuroi, too.
You're all alone, then?
Only for now. Kuroi said she'd catch up.
I can't wait much longer for her. I have to stop them.
Alright, stay put. I'll be there in a...
Iroha!
She was cut off.
Who's Iroha?
A friend. You saved us once before. She's the one in the hooded cloak.
Oh yeah, I'm glad she's safe.
She is, for now.
I have to get to her.
Hey, Sayaka.
Didn't you say you found Mami with the Magius?
Yeah.
Then if we help this girl out, maybe we'll find her.
What do you think?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, Chiel.
Is it cool if we come with you?
That Mami friend of yours might be there.
She almost killed you last time.
Yeah, I know. I remember.
It's given me the chills just thinking about it.
So what?
We can't leave Mami with them.
They brainwashed her.
And if they're drying witches here, we can't ignore that.
We can deal with both at the same time.
If Miss Tomoe were in her right mind, she'd do the same.
All right. Thank you.
Now, let's end this nonsense.
You see that, Nemu?
All those souls were tiny little sparks.
And now, they're gonna set fire to the whole world.
I didn't know playing with fire was what the wings of the Magius were created for.
What's wrong? You don't look happy.
If something's bothering you, let's hear it.
Toka, I'm begging you, please stop the operation.
We're dragging innocent people into something they're not a part of.
You've always been so kind and considerate.
You see what's happening out there.
It's not too late to stop this.
Actually, Mifuyu, when you think about it, no one's really innocent.
Humanity wouldn't have advanced as far as it has.
If magical girls hadn't sacrificed their lives.
That all ends here.
I won't allow them to use us for the sake of their progress when they don't even know about us.
I'm begging you, please stop this.
You're having second thoughts about it, because you don't understand.
But that's okay.
That's where I come in.
I call the shots.
You don't have to understand.
Just follow my lead.
I will not!
This has to stop right now!
Suruno, I need your help!
Suruno, don't!
I'm sorry, Mifuyu.
Whatever time I had is almost up.
I was wondering, Toka...
About what?
When this is all over, can we go to that theme park?
Mm-hmm.
This isn't the place for playing games.
Vivo o morto, especially.
Mm-hmm.
Alina.
That's all you can say?
No grazie?
Oh well.
I'm leaving this hovel and going back to my artillery.
You're leaving?
I committed to Toka and Nemu's grandiose plans because I thought they had soul.
But ultimately my goal as an artiste wasn't having tea parties in castles with girls who have the intelligence of sheep.
Anywho, if you survive to the climax, do ring me up.
I'd love to know how this all played out.
Arrivederci!
They got all the exits covered.
Hey.
I seen that girl before.
Are there any updates about this storm?
I'll check the weather.
Don't bother.
I got your forecast here.
Ta-da!
Good thinking.
We'll have clear skies.
Huh?
Come on, hop in.
Does everyone have their seatbelts fastened?
Yes, ma'am.
The supercell is heading straight for the northeast, bringing heavy rain and gusty winds.
It's currently moving north along the Pacific coast and growing even stronger.
This is turning out to be the biggest storm.
I, um, I don't want to worry anyone, but do you think it's possible Valpurgus Doct will show up in Kamehama?
I never thought of that.
Why would you think she'd come here?
Well, um, we were told once that she would appear in Mitakihara City during a big storm.
Since the Magius are luring witches from all over to here, maybe they'd accidentally attract her, too.
At this point, I wouldn't rule anything out.
If they did lure Valpurgus not here, then everyone in Kamehama, including us, are doomed.
Well, we shouldn't lose hope.
No matter how bad things look now, one of us could still save the day.
Yeah.
I know that as long as I have hope, I'll never regret being a magical girl.
We all feel the same, I'm sure.
Big time.
Ours is not a bad fate.
Better change.
Things are going to get bumpy from here on.
Okay.
Are you two ready back there?
We're ready.
Hang on tight, then.
Time for some offensive driving.
Wanna tell me what you think you're doing here?
Huh?
Oh, right.
I was just trying to get to that castle.
All by yourself?
That was the plan.
Someone has to stop them, and if I don't try, I know I'll regret it.
Yeah, well, you don't look tough enough to play the loner hero.
No offense or anything.
If they'd listen to anyone, I know they'd listen to me.
Why the heck would they?
Do you know those little brats or something?
Wait, did you talk to Nemo and the others?
Oh, no, I haven't.
I'm just telling it like it is and hoping this dumbass plan of theirs fails.
This isn't like them at all.
Something went wrong somewhere.
And I think if I can talk to them, maybe I can get them to stop.
That'll make it easier for you to get around.
Thanks, but like...
Who are you?
Hiroha Tamaki.
What a hit!
Indeed.
Miss Nanami!
That was too close.
Thanks, Homura.
It was nothing.
I'm glad you're both safe.
Now, we just have to figure out how to get in.
Everything seems to be going as we planned.
It's even better than we planned!
Iroha, can you hear me?
Iroha!
I hear you, Yachiyo.
Are you close?
Yes, I see the gate.
But getting through will be...
rather tricky.
Okay, hang on a sec.
I'll go and open it.
Wait, it's too dangerous.
I'll find another way in.
I need your help, and this is our only chance!
Besides, I'm almost there.
I can handle this!
I'm the only one who can.
Trust me!
Okay.
Can she get it open by herself?
Well, she sounded like she knew what she was doing.
She'll open it.
Open up the gate and hurry!
What?
No one gave us the order to open it.
I just gave it!
Please open up the gate!
Hurry up!
I said hurry up!
Yes, ma'am, right away.
I did it!
Irohatamaki!
Surrender now!
Now that was stupid!
What are you thinking?
I thought you left.
Surprise!
You won't live long taking risks like that.
Well, I'm not dead yet thanks to you.
You stayed to help, and I'm so grateful you did.
No time to get all mushy.
Come on, follow me.
Hey!
What are you doing?
We gotta go!
I became a magical girl in exchange for a wish,
just like you did.
I wanted this life!
This is the path I chose,
and I can't waste that wish!
I don't know what you wished for,
but after hearing all that,
I'd say it was an early grave.
Take my hand!
Let's connect our powers!
What?
Please!
I can't do this on my own!
All right.
But make it quick, okay?
You got it!
I'm not going to let the wish I made go to waste!
Jump in!
Hey!
What happened to our gate?
Can you see what's going on?
What?
That went way better than it could have.
Everyone was in top form today.
Yachiyo!
Oh, thanks, Iroha.
You did it.
Actually, it's all thanks to Kyoko here.
We heard you needed help.
We heard you needed help too many skills to hate.
To handle that is a very good lesson.
Well, everyone for sure you think that it's method B,
or anyone for
There is
I